How was the exam, Richard?
考试考得怎样,Richard?
Not too bad.
不算太坏,
I think I passed in English and Mathematics.
我想我的英语和数学及格了.
The questions were very easy.
题目很容易.
How about you, Gary?
Gary,你怎么样?
The English and Maths papers weren't easy enough for me.
英语和数学试题对我来说不很容易.
I hope I haven't failed.
我希望我别不及格.
I think I failed the French paper.
我想我的法语及不了格,
I could answer sixteen of the questions.
我能回答其中的16道题.
They were very easy.
这些题很容易.
But I couldn't answer the rest.
但我回答不出其余的题.
They were too difficult for me.
那些题对我来说太难了.
French tests are awful, aren't they?
法语太可怕了,你说呢?
I hate them.
我讨厌法语.
I'm sure I've got a low mark.
我的法语成绩肯定很低.
Oh, cheer up!
啊,别灰心!
perhaps we didn't do too badly.
或许我们考得还不太糟.
The guy next to me Wrote his name at the top of the paper.
坐在我旁边的那个人在试卷顶端写了自己的名字.
Yes?
是吗?
Then he sat there and looked at it for three hours!
然后他坐在那里,对着考卷看了3个小时,
He didn't write a word!
一个字也没写!